response-o-matic.com 2012-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Response-o-matic

##  Privacy Policy

Wondermill Webworks Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all Webmasters.org sites run by note.com LLC, including this website: Response-o-matic.com 

**Policies for Webmasters (Website Owners) Using our services:**  
Our sites' registration forms requires Webmasters  to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zipcode, country or language). We use contact information from the registration form to send the Webmaster "Service Mailings", from us only, which include legal notices, new features and valuable tips, as well as promotions about our company and our partners. The Webmaster's contact information is also used to contact them when necessary. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. 

As noted above, our Service Mailings include periodic notices to our member Webmasters regarding new features, legal notices, and valuable tips. Because the Service Mailings are the only method of sending legal notices to member Webmasters, a Webmaster cannot unsubscribe from Service Mailings without terminating his/her use of our service. 

**Policies for both Webmasters and Web Visitors**  
_Links to other sites_ : The advertisements on our site may contain links to other sites. **Response-o-matic.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Before submitting data to an advertiser site, it is the Web Visitor's responsibility to ascertain the advertiser's Privacy Policy and not submit the data if (s)he does not find it acceptable. 

_Cookies **:**_ Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to track users for the purposes of paying member sites registered with our Affiliate Program. Cookies are set from both this website as well as from the master domain, **Webmasters.org**. 

_Contests_ : We may run contests on our site in which we ask contest entrants for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zipcode, country or language). We use contact data from our contests to send entrants information and promotions, through mailings conducted by us only, about our company and our partners. The entrant's contact information is also used to contact the entrant when necessary. We may also use this data to tailor the entrant's experience at our sites, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Contest entrants may opt-out of receiving future mailings related to that contest; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We also have contractual arrangements with affiliate marketing networks, provide some of the advertisements shown on our sites. To find out more about how these networks handle the collection of personal information, please visit their provacy statements at: 

_IP Addresses:_ We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

**Security**  
We take the security of our data seriously and utilize several software and hardware devices to protect unauthorized access to our data. In addition, we monitor the use of our service to detect attempts at accessing our data. Any such attempts may be dealt with on a technical or legal level, as appropriate in a given case. 

**Supplementation of Information**  
This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For example, we may contract with a firm which identifies geographic locale of an IP address in order to better present the site (including our advertiser messages) in the appropriate language local to a Webmaster or Web Visitor.   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Wondermill Webworks Inc. 1199 Glen Tara Lane Victoria, BC V8Z 6Z4 Canada

THIS STATEMENT WAS CREATED ON MAY 1ST, 2005
